<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<resources>
	<string name="headline">Create your Actifit / Steem account</string>
	<string name="desc_part1">In order to use Actifit, you need an account on the Steem blockchain. If you do not have an account, you can sign up for one right now!<br/><p class="lead mb-2 p-2 text-center bg-danger text-white"><i>Don\'t know what Actifit is? Head over to <a href="https://actifit.io" class="acti-hover"><u>home page</u></a> to learn more</i></p>While you can create a Steem account from <a href="https://signup.steemit.com/?ref=actifit">Steemit.com</a> for free, it could take up to two weeks, or more to get approved.<br/>Other services allow the creation of Steem accounts at a cost, yet here at Actifit, <span class="afit-tokens-earned text-brand">for as low as</span></string>
	<string name="desc_part2"><span class="afit-tokens-earned text-brand">$</span>, you get the following awesome treats:<li>Your <span class="afit-tokens-earned text-brand">free Steem / Actifit account</span>, usable across the Steem blockchain and all cool relevant dapps such as Dtube, Steem monsters, Steem hunt, dlike, tasteem, and many more...</li></string>
	<string name="desc_part3"> AFIT tokens matching your current investment. The higher you invest, the higher the amount earned.The Steem blockchain requires a min amount of Steem Power (which decides how often you can do transactions on it). To help with that, <span class="afit-tokens-earned text-brand">we will delegate to your new account </span></string>
	<string name="desc_part4"><span class="afit-tokens-earned text-brand"> Steem Power for 3 months to help you post easily once per day!</span><li>Via posting your daily activity, you can earn STEEM upvotes and AFIT tokens, a free source of earning crypto while getting healthy and fit!</li>Owning AFIT tokens allows you to earn more rewards for your daily activity, as it <span class="afit-tokens-earned text-brand">increases your User Rank</span>. At the minimum </string>
	<string name="desc_part5">$ investment, your User Rank will stand at 3%. For instance, <span class="afit-tokens-earned text-brand">investing 100$ will earn you </span></string>
	<string name="desc_part6"><span class="afit-tokens-earned text-brand"> AFIT tokens</span>, and will increase your User Rank to 6%, reflecting in an <span class="afit-tokens-earned text-brand">increase in your daily STEEM and AFIT rewards.</span></string>
	<string name="buy_text"><div class="w-100 p-2">You can buy &amp; send STEEM using any of the following exchanges</div><div class="w-30 p-3"><a href="https://bittrex.com/" >Bittrex</a></div><div class="w-70 p-3"><a href="https://www.binance.com/" >Binance</a></div><div class="w-30 p-3"><a href="https://poloniex.com/" >Poloniex</a></div><div class="w-70 p-3"><a href="https://www.huobi.com/" >Huobi</a></div><div class="w-100 p-2">Or check out any of the other exchanges listed on <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/steem/#markets">Coinmarketcap</a></div></string>
</resources>